Privacy Policy
==============

December 6, 2013 / Freakden

Privacy Policy for Freakden.com
-------------------------------

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at [Privacy](mailto:info@freakden.com).

At www.Freakden.com we consider the privacy of our visitors to be extremely important. This privacy policy document describes in detail the types of personal information is collected and recorded by www.Freakden.com and how we use it.

**Log Files**  
Like many other Web sites, www.Freakden.com makes use of log files. These files merely logs visitors to the site – usually a standard procedure for hosting companies and a part of hosting services’s analytics. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet Service Provider (ISP), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and possibly the number of clicks. This information is used to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

**Cookies and Web Beacons**  
www.Freakden.com uses cookies to store information about visitors’ preferences, to record user-specific information on which pages the site visitor accesses or visits, and to personalize or customize our web page content based upon visitors’ browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

**Our Advertising Partners**

Freakden.com places and offers advertising spots to help generate income to keep the community thriving and free. Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site.

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology in their respective advertisements and links that appear on www.Freakden.com and which are sent directly to your browser. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons) may also be used by our site’s third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertising campaigns and/or to personalize the advertising content that you see on the site.

www.Freakden.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers or those links which are posted to the site by users of www.Freakden.com

**Third Party Privacy Policies**

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. www.Freakden.com’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites. What Are Cookies?

**Children’s Information: This Website is for ADULTS ONLY**  
We believe it is important to provide added protection for children online. We encourage parents and guardians to spend time online with their children to observe, participate in and/or monitor and guide their online activity. www.Freakden.com does not knowingly collect any personally identifiable information from children under the age of 18/21 nor do we allow anyone under the age of 18/21 to access our website or use it in anyway. If a parent or guardian believes that www.Freakden.com has in its database the personally-identifiable information please contact us immediately (using the contact in the first paragraph) and we will use our best efforts to promptly remove such information from our records. Only adults are able to access and use our websites. It is 100% for adults only.

**Online Privacy Policy Only**  
This privacy policy applies only to our online activities and is valid for visitors to our website and regarding information shared and/or collected there. This policy does not apply to any information collected offline or via channels other than this website. Browse and visit links completely at your own risk.

**Consent**  
By using our website, you hereby consent to our privacy policy and agree to its terms and agree that www.Freakden.com can not be held liable for any use of this website or any of the links contained on or outside of the site. You are also stating by accessing this website that you are a legal adult and legally can access this site.

**Update**  
This Privacy Policy was last updated on: Sunday, December 6th, 2015.  
_Should we update, amend or make any changes to our privacy policy, those changes will be posted here._

Category [Terms](https://www.freakden.com/blog/terms/)

#### Freakden Essentials

#### Newest Posts

* [Rate my cock-8.5 inches long, 6 inches thick-( if u think u can take it, dm me )](https://www.freakden.com/pin/rate-my-cock-8-5-inches-long-6-inches-thick-if-u-think-u-can-take-it-dm-me/)
* [Sissy Georgina in all her glory for the world to see. little clitty dripping in panties under gorgeous dress excited to be EXPOSED.](https://www.freakden.com/pin/sissy-georgina-in-all-her-glory-for-the-world-to-see-little-clitty-dripping-in-panties-under-gorgeous-dress-excited-to-be-exposed/)
* [The incidence of Klinefelter Syndrome is 1 in 500 to 650 male births. It is thought that 1 out of 4 Klinefelter Syndrome males have micropenis, but no one knows for sure. However, an adult male’s erect penis that measures (SPL) 3.67 inches (9.32cm) or less is considered by reputable medical orgs to be an “adult” micropenis. This 47,XXY subject’s erect penis is approx 3 inches (7.62cm) as shown. The most common sexual symptoms of XXY are small testes (a/k/a balls) and infertility. Other issues can include impotence, ED, gynecomastia, learning disabilities, youthful appearance with little body hair, and low testosterone. There are many other characteristics and more info can be obtained by searching online. However, there is no cure for it and the only way to determine if one has it is to have a special blood test called a “karyotype”. Most XXY males lead normal productive lives, but some have more severe symptoms which lead to poor health and sometimes addictions in an effort to cope.](https://www.freakden.com/pin/the-incidence-of-klinefelter-syndrome-is-1-in-500-to-650-male-births-it-is-thought-that-1-out-of-4-klinefelter-syndrome-males-have-micropenis-but-no-one-knows-for-sure-however-an-adult-males-ere/)

×

#### Welcome

Social Login

* * *

Username or Email 

Password ([Forgot?](https://www.freakden.com/login-lpw/)) 

or [Sign Up](https://www.freakden.com/signup/)

You need to enable Javascript.

By using this site you agree you're a legal adult.  
[ADVERTISE](https://www.freakden.com/pin/advertise/)·[BLOG](https://www.freakden.com/c/blog/)·[CONTACT](https://www.freakden.com/contact/)·[DMCA](https://www.freakden.com/pin/dmca-and-copyright-infringement/)·[PRIVACY](https://www.freakden.com/pin/privacy-policy/)  
[RULES](https://www.freakden.com/do-not-post-list/)·[TERMS](https://www.freakden.com/pin/terms-and-conditions/)·[HOW TO](https://www.freakden.com/pin/how-it-all-works/)·[FAQ](https://www.freakden.com/pin/faqs/)·[2257](https://www.freakden.com/pin/2257-compliance-statement/)  
Copyright © 2024 · Freakden
